ORIGINAL WORK BY TATSUYA ENDO
SERIALIZED ON SHUEISHA'S SHONEN JUMP PLUS
It's not going to work.
What?
Anya doesn't want this mother.
Franky, you're not suited
to playing the role of a mother.
With your skills,
couldn't you have done a better job?
There's only so much I can do
with your height and body.
I can't believe I did all this for you!
-Operation Strix.
-I'll give you some peanuts.
We passed the written exam to
infiltrate the prestigious Eden Academy,
for a top-secret assignment
given to me,
as an agent of Westalis Intelligence,
to stop the war plans of Desmond,
a key figure in Ostania.
But I had no idea that they'd require both
parents to be present at the interview.
Oh well…
I guess I'll get married.
SECURE A WIFE
Did you hear that
we might've been burgled?
I heard that all the women's
personal information files were ransacked.
How creepy is that?
I think our manager is creepier.
He was staring at me creepily
just this morning.
It's because
you're wearing such a short skirt.
What? Well, it makes my boyfriend happy.
Sharon, you have a nice body too,
you should show more leg!
You don't do such things
when you have a kid.
What do you think, Yor?
Isn't it creepy?
Hm?
Is that coffee for the manager?
We should put a booger in it!
Huh?
Will putting a booger in it
make it taste better?
Yor, you're so unique.
Wha--?
I agree! You're so odd that
men probably aren't attracted to you.
Hey, Millie.
Yor, you have great features,
so if you dress up more,
I'm sure you'll be popular!
Oh…
I'll introduce you to some of
my favorite cosmetics!
If I can keep my job,
that's good enough for me.
But you're already 27, aren't you?
You should be careful.
You know how
there's been a lot of spy activity?
Because of that, people have been
reporting even the smallest things.
Just the other day,
a woman in her late twenties was
reported by her neighbors saying she
was suspicious because she lives alone.
What? Really? How crazy!
Camilla, you're so well-informed!
I guess it is odd that she's alone
at that age. How suspicious.
I see. Thank you for the warning.
That's right! I'll be having a party
at my house this weekend!
You should come, Yor.
Of course, you're welcome to bring a date.
Don't you think you set the bar too high?
Maybe the creepy culprit who broke in here
would be willing to accompany her.
How mean!
Hello? Briar residence.
Hey sis! How are you?
Yuri!
How's work?
It's fine.
I'm still working at the same place!
You're a bit odd, so I'm worried.
I'm normal! How rude of you.
Are you thinking of marriage yet?
Is there anyone special?
That topic again?
Actually, I'm being offered a promotion,
so I'll be busy flying around
even more than I am now.
But I'm worried about leaving you,
so I'm debating whether to take it or not.
I'm the person I am today because of you,
and I'm grateful to you.
That's why I want you to be happy.
I know. Thanks, Yuri.
I can introduce you to someone.
What? No, it's fine!
In fact,
I'm going to a party this weekend!
Of course, with a date!
What? You have a boyfriend?
Yes! So don't worry about me.
I'm so glad! It's a party for work, right?
Yes, at Camilla's.
Oh! Then I'll have to talk to Dominic
and ask him what kind of guy he was!
Huh?
You're really gullible,
so I'll have to get rid of him
if he's a loser.
Huh? Um…
I'll put my promotion on pause
until I'm sure he's a good guy!
You don't have to do that!
I'll be looking forward to it!
Bye! Good night!
What shall I do?
I have to find someone for the party.
If he finds out I'm lying,
I'll lose even more credibility
because I'll be a freak and a liar.
I have to find someone good, so my
little brother will take the promotion!
Yuri, I was lying!
I was only joking earlier!
Oh? A rare sibling fight?
Oh, "Shopkeeper"?
I'm sorry, that was a mistake.
Good evening.
I have a client for you, Thorn Princess.
The Royal Hotel.
Room 1307.
I'm sorry, my lady.
This floor is currently reserved.
-Did someone order a woman?
-I don't know.
But I heard that
there was a traitorous bastard here.
What was that?
There's an intruder! It's a woman!
Excuse me, you're Deputy Secretary Brennan
of the Auditing Board, correct?
I'm terribly sorry,
but may I take your last breath?
Her codename is Thorn Princess.
She's an assassin.
She has been trained in
the art of killing from an early age,
and has continued to take on dirty jobs
at the behest of her employers.
It won't come out!
What? No! What am I going to do?
This is my only good dress!
How can I go to the party?
Is there anyone special?
I guess it is odd that she's alone
at that age.
Of course, you're welcome to bring a date.
It's impossible…
The only housework I'm good at is
cleaning up.
Scruffy!
I got a list of unmarried women
from City Hall for you.
Thanks.
A woman who's okay with children
and a divorcee, but with class worthy of
a prestigious school, and ready
to proceed with marriage within 48 hours.
I'd love to worship such a goddess
if she exists.
I'm not picky,
but I can't even get a date.
-How pathetic.
-Don't call me pathetic!
Are you at a disadvantage because of me?
Will Anya get in the way?
You won't be in the way.
Don't worry and go watch some TV.
Okay.
Why don't you just use a female agent
or someone from your agency?
The recent spy hunts have wiped out
most of them, so there's no one good.
Oh, because people are
all about snitching these days.
They're so understaffed that
another new assignment came my way.
They want me to destroy
a certain smuggling ring.
How dangerous is that?
Let's just hurry up and choose one.
The quickest way is to find someone
who wants to get married as well.
We can try to find their weakness. If
they don't have one, we can make one up.
I want to avoid unnecessary risks.
What are you saying?
She's already risky enough.
She doesn't look like a daughter
from a good family at all.
You're right. I have to do something
about her appearance.
I'll take her measurements,
so this way, young lady.
You're going to sell Anya!
If you're a good girl, I won't sell you.
Where does she learn to say those things?
The seamstress is married.
The mistress was on the list of
unmarried women earlier,
but she has history of
an arrest for political campaigning,
which will pose a risk.
When it comes to favorable conditions,
it's not easy.
Excuse me!
Oh, Yor! Long time no see!
Hello. I want you to fix my dress.
May I ask you to rush it?
Of course, since you're a regular here.
How did she sneak up behind me?
Who is she?
Yor… Yor… There she is.
Yor Briar, 27 years old.
No history of marriage or divorce.
Both her parents are deceased,
but she has a younger brother.
They're both public servants
and their backgrounds aren't suspicious.
Maybe I didn't notice her
because I've been a bit careless lately.
Um… You've been staring at me.
Did you need something?
What? She noticed I was observing her?
Oh! I'm sorry…
I was just thinking how beautiful you are.
Does that mean you like my appearance?
Huh? Well, yes.
Yor, you have great features, so if you
dress up more, I'm sure you'll be popular!
Um--
Father! We measured Anya's length!
Oh, who's she?
Another customer.
He has a child…
I almost invited someone's spouse.
I've heard that actions like that can
get you killed by the wife.
In my case, I'd just kill them back, but…
Huh?
No, no. People will find out
that I'm an assassin if I keep on
thinking like this.
I need to become more normal.
Assassin?
Spy? Assassin? Anya is…
excited!
The girl was hungry for entertainment.
I thought about taking her as my wife,
but maybe not.
I was hoping to have him
be my date for the party,
but I'll have to abort to avoid drama.
Oh, Anya's so sad that
she doesn't have a mother!
Why so suddenly?
I miss the presence of a mother!
You're not here with your wife?
Oh… no.
My wife died two years ago, so
I've been raising her as a single father.
I won't be killed even if I invite him?
Um!
Pretend to be your boyfriend?
Yes. I lied to my brother
and told him that I have a boyfriend.
If it is not too much trouble, I'd like to
ask if you could come to a party with me…
I don't have
any ulterior motives or anything!
And of course, I'll thank you properly.
I just want to
give my brother peace of mind.
Okay. I'll accept.
Really?
However, I'd like to
ask you for something in return.
Therefore,
we'd like to ask you to pretend to
be her mother for the interview.
A mother?
In these uncertain times, I want
my daughter to get into a good school.
That is also the wish of my late wife.
Father's a liar.
What a wonderful person!
First, I'll get her to agree
to a small request,
and then I'll eventually get her to
agree to a formal marriage.
I'll do whatever I can.
Thank you.
Then I'll see you at Saturday's party.
Okay.
I requested a babysitter for Saturday,
so be good, okay?
Stock up on peanuts!
Fine.
Here. Ten pents change, ribbit.
Thank you, ribbit!
Ribbit?
T? No. An F cipher.
Additional mission details?
Recover art stolen from the West
and destroy the smuggling ring.
Execution is at 6 p.m. on Saturday
when the target contacts the buyer.
Saturday?
Therefore,
we have to finish this quickly, so I can
make it to the party in time. Help me.
Wait! I'm just an informant,
my fighting skills are garbage!
And you hardly ever pay me for anything!
Seventy-eight works of art worth
a total of three million dalcs.
I'm sure they won't notice
one or two of them missing.
Leave it to me.
I'm the guy who invented
new spy stuff for a day like this!
How useful.
Loid is late…
I hope he's not been
in an accident or anything…
You didn't tell me
there would be so many of them!
There are 38 of them.
I can't spend more than
ten seconds on each person!
It's endless!
I packed everything! Get in!
Woo!
Now, which one shall I have?
I'll have this one.
A diamond! That's not fair!
That looks expensive!
It'll be part of my disguise.
Shut up and give it back!
I see… I guess
this is what they call "being played."
For my brother's sake, I must maintain
good relationships at my workplace.
Therefore, I can't afford
to miss this party.
You're late, Yor!
I'm sorry. This is for you.
Huh?
I heard you were bringing your boyfriend.
He had some urgent business to attend to.
What! How disappointing!
I wanted to meet him!
What kind of excuse was that?
It makes me cringe!
I knew for sure she was
bluffing about having a man.
Shall we report her for being a liar?
Yes!
She must be a spy used to
lower the birth rate in our country!
What? What a lame tale.
She's just a girl who can't get a man.
Just ignore her.
Aw, I was so excited
to meet your boyfriend.
D-Dominic.
Since Yuri's always worried about you.
Um… Could you tell my brother that
I brought a nice man?
What? No way!
Do you really want to go that far?
That'll just make you seem more miserable.
-Hey, stop Camilla!
-Stop chatting with someone else's man!
I'll be honest with your little brother
and tell him you came alone.
Will she benefit in some way
from doing that?
What a nuisance.
If all the adults here die,
my brother won't have to find out…
I'm sorry. Have fun while you're here!
Come on, Camilla. Help me cook the gratin.
And that guy…
Mommy!
My older son here is taking the
entrance exam for Eden Academy this year!
How amazing!
-He's going to be an elite!
-That must be what it's like.
To be normal…
I guess my brother
wanted me to be like them.
Hey, she's still here.
How is she so mentally strong?
I can't believe she had the courage
to come alone.
I see. I guess I don't belong here.
I'm sorry,
I'm going to excuse myself--
I'm sorry I'm late!
I'm Loid Forger, Yor's husband.
Um, you don't have to be my husband.
Just my boyfriend…
Oh, shoot!
I got it confused with my mission.
Oh, Mr. Forger. You're bleeding…
Oh, sorry. One of my emergency patients
got a bit out of control.
It's quite common
in the field of psychiatry.
Were you having fun, Yor?
You must be joking.
You are married, Yor?
Why didn't you say anything?
Uh… Well…
It's a bit embarrassing, but I was
once married and I have a child,
so maybe she was just a bit concerned…
This can't be true! There's no way
Yor has such a handsome husband!
I'm going to humiliate her!
Yor! The gratin is fresh out of the oven!
Oops! I slipped!
It's good that you value food,
but it's rude to use your feet, Yor.
I'm sorry!
-That's what they got out of this?
-This is good!
Yes, it is.
Mr. Ranger, did you know?
It's Forger.
I heard she had a shady job
before she came to the government job!
-What was it?
-Stop it!
Men would call you and you'd go to hotels
to give them massages? How scandalous!
That was…
I was called in to stab someone
disguised as an acupuncturist…
No, she's got it wrong, Loid. I…
-It's admirable.
-Huh?
Yor lost her parents when she was young
and had to work hard to
look after her younger brother.
It requires more than just determination
to endure and continue hard work
for the sake of someone or something,
at the expense of oneself.
That's something
she should be proud about.
-Let's go home, Yor.
-Okay.
Thank you for the delicious food.
I'm sorry I said husband…
Oh, no problem.
What should we say
if word gets to your brother?
Well, Loid…
This is just an idea, but…
What?
Are they remnants of the smuggling ring?
-Hold on tight, Yor!
-Huh?
How did they know where we were?
Was there a tracker in the art?
You're being really careless
these days, Twilight!
Who are they?
Um…
It seems like my patient's hysteria
has not subsided yet.
It must be hard being a doctor.
She believed that?
Let's get away for now.
The van is abandoned.
They must be hiding somewhere.
Let's split and find them!
Yor, come this way!
Is it okay to punch your patients?
Well, um…
It's a new treatment method in the medical
field called concussive therapy.
I see.
I don't know if she's sharp or dull.
Be careful, Yor!
Another one? I can't get him--
I'm sorry! I'm an amateur,
yet I just treated a patient!
I'm actually good at self-defense
and stuff. My brother taught me and…
Thank you, Yor!
How amazing! You sent him flying!
I'm sorry for sending him flying.
There they are!
Don't go easy on them! Finish them!
Um, Loid. I'm sorry to bring this up
at a time like this,
but would you like to get married?
What?
Just something like
an extension of our terms…
Apparently single women, such as myself
are found to be suspicious,
so to blend in…
In order to continue my job
as an assassin as well.
What I'm trying to say is…
Rather than just ending it
after the interview,
what about making it official?
For our mutual benefit!
He's probably the only person
who'll accept me for who I am.
Then let's stop by City Hall on
the way home and get the process started.
Now?
Strike while the iron is hot.
Oh, that's right.
Where did I drop it?
Bastards!
We found them!
Shoot 'em dead!
Yor, in times of sickness…
and in times of sorrow,
whatever difficulties may come.
-Let us help each other.
-Yes.
As long as my assignment…
My assassinations…
last.
PREPARE FOR THE EXAM
Subtitle translation by: Nana Onishi